<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Yorvick of The Forsaken</title>
    <link href="https://niirvil.github.io/yorvick-the-forsaken/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://niirvil.github.io/yorvick-the-forsaken" />
    <updated>2025-03-11T06:42:21+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Yorvick</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://niirvil.github.io/yorvick-the-forsaken</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Tirisfal Glades and The Awakening</title>
        <author>
            <name>Yorvick</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://niirvil.github.io/yorvick-the-forsaken/tirisfal-glades-and-the-awakening.html"/>
        <id>https://niirvil.github.io/yorvick-the-forsaken/tirisfal-glades-and-the-awakening.html</id>

        <updated>2025-03-11T06:42:21+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I was awakend from the tomb in Deathknell by Undertaked Mordo, not exactly sure what had happened but I still realized that I had my&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    I was awakend from the tomb in Deathknell by Undertaked Mordo, not exactly sure what had happened but I still realized that I had my arcane skills intact yet weakened.<br>Seems like they were ready to discard me into the fires with the others that were not.. so conscious. Mordo was kinda enough to guide me to speak with<br>Sarvis the shadow priest at the chapel in town.<br><br>Sarvis led me on with the current events, Sylvanas was our new leader and saviour from the grasps of Lich King, neat.<br>Seems like the task that is asked from us is clear, rid the scourge and.. humans? Humanity and mortality, those thoughts are long forgotten now..<br><br>Clearing the surrounding forest of bats and wolves was easy enough, some mumbling mindless undead and skeletons were rampant too which I took quick care of.<br>Few fleeting thoughts of the past life flew by me when I took care of these tasks, especially the undead, but I tried to pay no mind to these things, not my concern anymore I thought.<br>Yet still something was nagging in back of my head.. Redpath and the culling of Darrowshire, I could not forget that what happened, yet I still didn't mind it anymore like I maybe would have in the past.<br>This is my new "life" now, I should let the thoughts of Redpath and Darrowshire fade away.<br><br>One particular task that was given to me was finding Samuel Fipps remains and bury it besides his late wife Marla's  grave. Samuel and Marla were a couple<br>before the scourge came and went, Marla was give swift death by her beloved husband Samuel, poetic. Yet even at her dying breath she wished to be buried with her husband..<br>This sorta behaviour puzzles me, why would she want that? Love? Perhaps.. Oh I also was asked to take down Samuels pals while at it, they were there too, rambling and shambling around mindleslly.<br><br>I was given a wand for a token of appreciation of my work, this will be handy since my powers are still weak, yet I'm starting to remember basic spells again.<br>There are alot of others that had strong enough mind to be freed from numbing dream of lich king, alot of them. So I collected some much needed equipment from around the town to be given for all the new recruits, we will make an fine addition to Lady Sylvanas growing army.<br>After finishing the tasks I had been given I booked a room from upstairs to rest a bit.. At least I thought I wanted to "rest", maybe something from the past life that still stayed with me, for I do not need resting anymore. Maybe just being with myself for a moment to clear my head with all this will be good. Yes, that is what I had in the past, solitude and quiet in the woods.. That is what I liked, should I still pursue that?
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
